Helen Lindberg

Full Stack Developer

Helen Lindberg

1765 5th St E Saint Paul. MN 55106

612.601.3914

helenilindberg@yahoo.com

Profile

As a detail-oriented and quality-driven web development student, I look forward to incorporating my 9+ years of management and customer service experience with my new technical skills in exciting and creative ways.

Skills

- ~Javascript, jquery, html, css, ajax, node.js
- ~Word, excel, access, powerpoint
- ~Creative solutions, leadership, customer service

Education

University of Minnesota/ Coding Certification

Program completion May of 2021, Online

Currently enrolled in the full stack coding and web development program learning javascript, jquery, html, css, ajax, node.js.

Saint Paul College / AAS

August 2015 - May 2018, Saint Paul, MN

Graduated from the medical office professional program with honors.

Employment

Swede Hollow Cafe / General Manager

April 2012 - Present, Saint Paul, MN

Hiring, employee training, task delegation, food safety, inventory, money handling, payroll.

Experience Gusto/ Project Coordinator

August 2016 - September 2017, Minneapolis, MN

Ensuring projects were completed on time and within budget, maintained project documentation, scheduled and attended meetings; reported to management and stakeholders regarding project progress.

Links

GitHub: https://github.com/HelenIL

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lindberghelen/

Portfolio: https://helenil.github.io/Portfolio/